《生活大爆炸》前情提要
Previously on The Big Bang Theory...
我得到了普林斯顿大学的夏季研究奖学金
I was offered a summer research fellowship at Princeton.
很不错的大学
A fine institution.
阿尔伯特·爱因斯坦教过书的地方
The place where Albert Einstein taught,
莱纳德也是在那里拿到博士学位
and where Leonard got his PhD,
所以那学校可能没落了
so it may have gone downhill.
各位  还记得诺维茨基博士吗
Gentlemen, you may remember Dr. Nowitzki.
她又回来加州理工读博士后啦
She's back at Caltech for her postdoc.
问一下  你是想和我发展恋爱关系吗
Question. are you seeking a romantic relationship with me?
如果我是呢
What if I were?
这会引起一系列的问题
Well, that would raise a number of problems.
我们是同事  我现在有女友
We're colleagues, I'm currently in a relation...
艾米  艾米
Amy? Amy.
艾米
Amy?
时至今日
你愿意嫁给我吗
Will you marry me?
请稍等我一下
One moment, please.
不是吧  你要在这节骨眼接电话吗
Really, you're going to answer that right now?
是莱纳德打来
It's Leonard.
我不想失礼嘛
I don't want to be rude.
你好
Hello?
你上哪去了
Oh, hey, where you been?
打你电话找你好久了
We've been calling you for hours.
抱歉  我的手机之前开了飞行模式
Oh, I'm sorry, my phone was on "Airplane" mode.
为什么
Why?
因为我在飞机上"飞行"啊
Because I was on an airplane.
开免提
Hey, put him on speaker.
你去哪里了
Yeah. ?Hey, where are you?
我来普林斯顿大学找艾米
I came to Princeton to see Amy.
说来也挺有意思
It's a funny story, actually.
我当时在跟诺维茨基博士共进午餐
I was having lunch with Dr. Nowitzki,
然后她亲吻了我
and she kissed me.
-什么  -啥
- Excuse me? - What?
你说什么
I'm sorry?
在那一刻我意识到
And in that moment, I realized
艾米才是我余生
that Amy was the only woman I ever wanted to kiss
唯一想亲吻的女人
for the rest of my life.
所以我来新泽西跟她求婚
So I came to New Jersey to ask her to marry me.
你真是太甜了
Oh, that's so sweet.
-谢尔顿...  -不过呢
- Sheldon... - Yeah, although
我的确是先去征求了某位男士的祝福
there was one man whose blessing I needed first.
我想过了  我确实想要
I've thought about it, and I really want to spend
与艾米共度余生
the rest of my life with Amy.
你会祝福我吗
Do I have your blessing?
谢尔顿
Well, Sheldon...
我觉得你应该将她的手指变成土星
...I think you should make her finger like Saturn
再往她手指上套个土星"环"
and put a ring on it.
你去问了霍金博士而不是艾米父亲吗
You asked Stephen Hawking and not her father?
霍金博士是个天才
Stephen Hawking's a genius.
如果他不支持  我才不要浪费时间去问她爹呢
If he said no, I wasn't gonna waste my time on her father.
那你有问过我父亲吧
But you did ask my father?
有  他同意
I did. He said yes.
但不是用机械人式语音说的  所以没那么酷
Although, not in a robot voice, so it wasn't nearly as cool.
我的天啊  真不敢相信你们订婚了
Okay. Oh, my God, I can't believe you guys are engaged.
还没订上婚呢
We're not engaged, yet.
这都半天了她还不回答我
She's taking forever to answer.
那是因为你在讲电话
Because you're on the phone!
我们稍后回电
We'll call you back.
她同意了
She said yes.
恭喜你们
Yay! ?Congratulations!
第十一季  第一集
母亲  我有好消息与你分享
Mother, I have some good news to share.
我们订婚啦
We're engaged.
我真为你们开心  但我一点都不惊讶
I am so happy for you two, but I'm not surprised.
我为此事祈祷多时了
I've been praying for this.
这件事上帝没半点功劳
Well, God had nothing to do with it.
完全是因为我跟别的女人接了吻
It happened because I was kissing another woman,
令我意识到我想跟艾米共度余生
and it made me realize I wanted to be with Amy.
居然有超过一名女性对你有兴趣
More than one woman was interested in you?
我可能祈祷太猛了
I might have prayed a little too hard.
等等  我想先...
Wait, oh, and I just...
我想现在就跟你说清楚
I want to let you know right now
我们不会在教堂里成婚
that we are not getting married in a church.
没关系  谢尔顿
That's all right, Sheldon.
耶稣在哪里  那便是教堂
Anywhere Jesus is is a church.
但他不会在我们婚礼上
Well, he won't be at our wedding.
他会在我心里  所以只要我人在
He's in my heart, so if I'm there,
他就在
he'll be there.
行  那他就是你带的伴
Okay, well, then, he's your plus-one.
你带人的名额就用完了
You don't get to bring anyone else.
没关系  爱你
That's fine. Love you.
我也爱你  再见
Love you, too. Bye.
主啊  谢谢您
Lord, thank you.
虽然您无所不能
Even though you can do anything,
但这事真显出了您的无上威能
that was mighty impressive.
我们订婚了
We're engaged.
天啊  太棒了
Oh, my God, that's amazing!
慢着  快告诉我整个经过
Wait, uh, tell me everything.
是这样的  诺维茨基博士亲了我
Well, Dr. Nowitzki was kissing me...
你可以别再用这事当故事开头了
Okay, you can stop leading with that part of the story.
恭喜你们啊
Well, congratulations.
太为你们俩高兴了
I'm so happy for you two.
稍等  我得告诉伯纳黛特
Hold on, I have to tell Bernadette.
妮妮  你猜怎么着
Hey, Bernie, guess what?
谢尔顿跟艾米订婚啦  你敢信吗
Sheldon and Amy got engaged. Can you believe it?
天啊  我真不敢相信
Oh, my God. I cannot believe it.
她好像高兴到...  在喜极而泣啊
She's so happy... I think she's crying.
你觉得谢尔顿会想要办一场
Do you think Sheldon's gonna want
奇葩的《星舰迷航》风婚礼吗
some weird Star Trek wedding?
我不知道
I don't know.
莱纳德当时想说
Well, Leonard could barely finish the words
"《神秘博士》婚礼蛋糕"
"Doctor Who wedding cake"
还没说完就被我狠狠拒绝
before I shut that down hard.
你有在听我说话吗
Are you listening to me?
有啊  你对莱纳德毫无人性  我听到了
Yeah, you're mean to Leonard. I heard you.
你还好吗
Is everything okay?
我要告诉你一件事
Look, I'm gonna tell you something,
但你不许惊慌失措
but you can't freak out,
因为我已经很手足无措了
because I'm already freaking out.
天啊  什么事
Oh, my God, what is it?
我又怀孕了
I'm pregnant again.
什...
Wha...
有点儿意思
Interesting.
霍华德知道了会疯的
Howard's gonna lose his mind.
慢着  你还没告诉他吗
Wait, you haven't told him yet?
没有
No.
你第一个告诉我吗  妮妮小亲亲
You told me first? Oh, Bernie!
这事不应该啊  我们很小心的
This wasn't supposed to happen-- we were careful.
对啊  我本来还以为哺乳期内
Yeah, I didn't even think you could get pregnant
女人是不会怀孕的呢
while you were breastfeeding.
结果呢  老娘就怀了
Well, guess what? You can.
好吧  听着  这是桩好事
Okay, look, look, this is a good thing.
这样哈雷就会有个弟弟
Halley's gonna have a little brother
或者妹妹陪她玩了
or sister to play with.
我想那应该是会挺有爱
I guess that would be pretty cute.
你知道吗  我也是我爸妈的意外之喜
And, you, know, I was a surprise to my parents,
我爸说我是发生在他们身上
and my dad said it was the best thing
最美好的事
that ever happened to them.
好吧  也许这个宝宝是上天的恩赐
Okay. Maybe this baby actually is a blessing.
天啊  亲爱的  当然了
Oh, my God, honey, of course it is.
我怎么会又怀上了呢
How am I pregnant again?
对啊  你们怎么搞的
Yeah, what were you thinking?
机票确认好了
All right, I'm all checked in to my flight.
你要走了我好难过
Well, I'm sad you're leaving.
为什么你订当天来回呢
Why'd you only book a flight for one day?
我来是为了求婚
I came here to propose.
要是你拒绝我  我可不想
If you'd said no, I wouldn't want to stick around
留下来看着你的蠢样
looking at your stupid face.
是这样的  只有你拒绝我的情况下
Now, mind you, your face is only stupid
你才会是一脸蠢样
in the "No" version of the story.
但我答应了  现在能享用你这货一辈子
But I said yes, so I get a lifetime of this.
是啊  聪明样
Yes, you do, smart face.
不如你多待几天吧
Why don't you stay a few extra days?
我没带别的衣服
Well, I don't have any other clothes.
我们可以去买
We'll get you some.
不要了吧  我这个人很挑的
Oh, I don't know, I'm pretty particular.
离这儿不到1600米的地方有家漫画店
Well, there's a comic book store less than a mile from here.
棒  买买买
Perfect, let's go shopping.
对了  我今晚要跟同事共进晚餐
Oh, um, and I'm having dinner with some colleagues tonight.
他们会很高兴见到你的
I'm sure they'd love to meet you.
来嘛  好不好
Come on, what do you say?
你开始用烦我的招数了
Aw, you're nagging me.
感觉我们已经结婚了似的
It's like we're already married.
那到底好不好嘛
Is that a yes or a no?
天啊  留点力等蜜月了再叨逼叨吧
Geez, save some for the honeymoon.
瞧  那是诺维茨基
Look at Nowitzki over there.
不敢相信她想从艾米身边
I can't believe she tried to steal Sheldon from Amy.
瞧好了
You know what?
我要过去告诉她  他们订婚了
I'm gonna go there and tell her that they're engaged now
她的小把戏落空了
and that her little plan didn't work.
这是因为你想维护谢尔顿
Because you're sticking up for Sheldon,
还是因为你还在气她拒绝了你
or because you're still mad she rejected you?
距离太远  听不到你在讲什么
Too far away, can't hear you.
你好  拉蒙娜
Hello, Ramona.
你好
Hello.
怎么独自一人坐在这呢
Why are you sitting by yourself?
我知道了
Oh, that's right,
谢尔顿在新泽西  他和艾米订婚了
Sheldon's in New Jersey being engaged to Amy.
我听说了
I heard.
现在谢尔顿闪边去了
Now that Sheldon's out of the picture,
我可以再给你个机会跟我约会
I could give you one more chance to go out with me.
谢邀  不用了
Nope, I'm good.
你确定吗
You sure?
小爷可不会再问第二次
I will not ask again.
我真心希望你不会再问了
I sincerely hope not.
行吧
Very well.
那在气氛变尴尬之前我先撤了
I'm going to leave before this gets awkward.
要我做晚饭吗
Want me to make dinner?
好啊  不过你能先坐下来吗
Uh, sure, but first, why don't you have a seat?
我有东西给你看
There's something I need to show you.
是晚饭教程的话就完美了
Ooh, if it's how to make dinner, that'd be great.
这是...  验孕棒吗
Is this a... pregnancy test?
是的
Yes.
这表示...  有了吗
That means... positive?
是的
Yes.
不是吧
No.
是的
Yes.
不  不是
N-- No.
是的
Yes.
别啊
No!
这怎么可能发生呢
How could this even happen?
我们这么小心
Uh, w-- we were careful.
-就是发生了  -不可能
- Well, it did. - ?No!
-我不能接受  -接受现实吧
-Yes! Yes! - ?No! No!
好吧  好吧  行吧
Okay! Okay! Okay!
那我们该怎么办
Well, w-what are we gonna do?
什么叫"我们该怎么办"
What do you mean what are we gonna do?
我们又要生一个宝宝了
We're gonna have another baby.
-不  不  -别叫了
- No! No! ?- Stop that!
-就是怀了  -我也想不叫啊
?- Yes! - No, I'm trying!
我知道这感觉很可怕  但是
Look, I know it's scary, but...
我们都是负责任的成年人  我们能行
we're both responsible adults, we can do this.
你真这么想吗
You really think so?
不
No!
-你好  斯图尔特  -你好  拉杰
- Hey, Stuart. - Oh, hey, Raj.
有什么能帮到你的
What can I help you with?
我要买一份订婚礼物
I need to buy an engagement gift.
那你来错地方了
Well, you came to the wrong place.
是送给谢尔顿和艾米的
It's for Sheldon and Amy.
-不是吧  他们订婚了  -是的
- No way! They're engaged? - Yeah.
真是个令人激动的好消息
Well, that's exciting news.
谁能想到谢尔顿和艾米会是下一对
Who would've thought Sheldon and Amy would be the next two
喜结连理的呢
to tie the knot?
可不是嘛  我才是那个
Tell me about it. I'm the one
通常是女生抢捧花,抢到捧花的人会延续幸福/最快下一个结婚
在莱纳德和佩妮婚礼上接到捧花的人
who caught the bouquet at Leonard and Penny's wedding.
好吧
Okay.
我看看
Uh... you know,
他们可能会喜欢这个
they might like this.
超人和神奇女侠  挺浪漫的
Superman and Wonder Woman, it's kind of romantic.
其实呢
You know what?
我干嘛给他们买礼物
Why am I buying them a gift?
他们已经拥有爱了
They have love.
幸福脱单的都去死吧
Screw them and their happiness.
你有没有适合苦逼单身狗的东西
What do you have for someone who's bitter and alone?
基本上全部都是
Literally everything.
谢尔顿  这两位是我研究小组的领导
Sheldon, these are the heads of my research team.
-你好  -赞恩博士  哈里斯博士
- Oh, hello. - Dr. Zane, Dr. Harris,
这是我未婚夫  谢尔顿·库珀博士
this is my fiance, Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
我第一次这样叫他
That's the first time I've said that
我都荡漾得起鸡皮疙瘩了
and it kind of gave me the goose bumps.
库珀博士
Dr. Cooper,
很高兴能见到你
we are so excited to meet you.
太客气了
Well, that's very kind of you.
想要的话  饭后我可以在你们的菜单上签名
If you'd like, I could autograph your menus after dinner, yeah?
但最好别让我发现你们拿去网上拍卖
But I better not see those on eBay.
不不  我们只是很开心能见到
No, no, no, we're just excited to meet the man
赢得这位才华横溢女士的男人
who landed this brilliant woman here.
那一点都不难
That wasn't hard,
是她倒贴我的
she threw herself at me.
但要让宇宙向我展露"私密"
Now, getting the universe to show me its naughty bits,
那才需要费一番功夫
that-that took some doing.
谢尔顿是物理学家
Sheldon's a physicist.
挺不错啊
Oh, that's nice.
艾米  我最近读了你
Amy, I recently read your paper on lesions
关于嗅觉受体损伤的论文
in the olfactory receptors in the brain.
非常富有创见
It was inspired.
看来水平不算太臭
Oh, well, I guess it didn't stink.
但即使臭了  那只老鼠也闻不到
But if it did, that rat wouldn't have known it.
抱歉
?I'm sorry,
你肯定不想坐在这儿
I'm sure you don't want to sit here
听我们聊工作
and listen to a bunch of work talk.
不  我很喜欢
Oh, no, I love it.
我们来聊工作吧
No, but let's talk about work.
艾米的工作  我的工作
Amy's work, my work.
不如就先聊我的工作吧
Yeah, why don't we start with my work?
我还真有个问题想问库珀博士
Actually, I do have a question for Dr. Cooper.
艾米首次告诉你她对突触追踪的切入点时
When Amy first told you about her approach to synaptic tracing,
你有意料到会给这个领域带来巨大变革吗
did you think it was gonna revolutionize the field?
不是吧
Really?
你要问的就是这个吗
That's your question?
怎么  你是综艺节目《今夜娱乐》的人吗
What are you, Entertainment Tonight?
这样吧
You know what?
我来给你提供一个更好的问题  听着
Let me give you a better question. Here,
"库珀博士
um, "Dr. Cooper,
听说你正在为美国军方
I heard you were working on a top-secret project
研究一个最高机密项目
for the U.S. Military.
不如跟我们说说这个吧"
Why don't you tell us about that?"
这才是个好问题
See, that's a great question.
好吧  那项目怎么样
Okay, what was that like?
我不能告诉你  那可是最高机密
Oh, I can't tell you that, it's top-secret.
刚才好心累
Boy, that was exhausting.
无意冒犯  但你的同事很无礼
You know, no offense, but your colleagues were pretty rude.
是吗  是他们无礼吗
Really, they were rude?
是啊
Yes.
他们只会一直说你的事  说你有多了不起
They just kept talking about you and how great you are,
完全无视我多次提起我自己
no matter how many times I brought me up.
他们是我的同事
You know, these are my colleagues
想谈论我的工作成果
and they want to talk about my work.
这有什么好让你不爽的
Why does that bother you so much?
因为我也在场啊
Because I was there.
就像请《变形金刚》的擎天柱来吃饭
It's like having Optimus Prime over to dinner
却不叫他变身卡车一样
and not asking him to turn into a truck.
你知道吗  谢尔顿
You know what, Sheldon?
你并非永远都是房间里最聪明的人
You're not always the smartest person in every room.
你很可能都不是这房间里最聪明的人
You may not even be the smartest person in this room.
不好意思
Oh, I am sorry.
著名天体物理学家
难道尼尔·德格拉塞·泰森躲在沙发后面吗
What, is Neil deGrasse Tyson hiding behind the couch?
如果真是  他也没多聪明
'Cause if he is, he's not that smart,
因为后面挺多灰的
it's pretty dusty back there.
你要去哪里
Hey, where are you going?
我要气冲冲地回我的房间
I'm storming off to my room.
那我能气冲冲地走去哪儿
Well, then where am I supposed to storm off to?
你那么聪明  怎么不自己想
Well, you're so smart, why don't you figure it out?
还有其他卧室吗
Is there another bedroom?
或者小房间之类的
Perhaps a-a den?
你们对你子宫里那个新事件
So, how are you guys doing with all the new
适应得怎么样
events in your womb?
挺好的
Good, you know?
很明显这事我们也没预料到
Obviously, it was a surprise.
发生了一些哭泣和争吵
There was some crying and some yelling.
有些打和好炮的提议被拒绝了
Some suggestion of make-up sex that did not go over well,
哪怕我们并不会怀上加怀
even though it's not like we can get more pregnant.
但我们意识到这是一份礼物
But then we realized that it's a gift, in the sense
虽然我们没有主动要求
that we didn't ask for it,
也没有主动选择
and we may not have chosen it...
而且我们已经有一个了
And we already have one.
每当我买到喜欢的衣服
You know, whenever I find a top I like,
我就会回去再买一件同款不同色的
I always go back and get a second one in a different color.
希望你们的宝宝不会是不同色
Which I hope is not the case with your baby.
我知道你们吓坏了  但你们是很好的父母
I know you guys are freaked out, but you're great parents,
你们如果需要帮忙  我们随时都在
and if you ever need help, we are here for you.
是啊  不管什么忙  开口就是了
Yeah, anything at all, just ask.
你知道你们能做什么吗
Ooh, you know what you could do?
你们可以也生个宝宝
You could have a baby, too.
不好意思  你说什么
I'm sorry, what?
真是个好主意  我们可以一起经历这个过程
No, that's a great idea, we could go through it together.
那一定会很好玩  对吧
Wouldn't that be fun?
你们刚刚才在说
You guys were just saying
你们有多害怕多凄惨
how freaked out and miserable you are.
我经常说疯话
I say a lot of crazy things.
毕竟我怀孕了  体内激素发生变化
I'm pregnant and hormonal.
快点  生个宝宝  干起来
Do it! Have a baby, do it!
那画面超级萌  我们的孩子在一起玩耍
Come on, it'd be so cute, our kids playing together?
怎么样  你们俩快去把床单滚起
What do you say, why don't you two hit the old mattress
赶紧搞出个娃娃来
and whip up a family?
我们才不会为了让你们开心
Okay, we're not gonna have a baby
就赶紧生孩子呢
just to make you guys feel better.
想让我俩生孩子  除非是我们准备好了
Yeah, if we're gonna have a baby it's gonna be when we are ready,
或者我确定佩妮要抛弃我了
or when I'm certain Penny is gonna leave me.
没错
Exactly.
他们都是我的朋友  我应该为他们高兴
They're my friends, and I should be happy for them.
我也努力过了
A-And I'm trying,
但我只感到满腹纠结和莫名的空虚
but all I feel is this gnawing, empty sensation in my gut.
我也曾有过这种感觉
I had that once.
后来发现是我肚里长了绦虫
Turned out it was a tapeworm.
好吧...
Cool. Uh...
只是...  这种事很难跟其他朋友聊
It's just...it's hard talking to my other friends about this,
但我想你可以理解我
but I knew you would understand.
为什么
Why is that?
因为你和我都是单身狗
Because you and I are both alone,
想想还真是抚慰人心
which is actually kind of comforting,
至少我们单着的路上有个伴
because at least we can be alone together.
这真是太尴尬了
Mm. This is-this is awkward.
我今晚本来打算提早关店
I, um, I was actually gonna close up a little early tonight
因为我要去约会
'cause I have a date.
真的吗
Really?
真的
Yeah.
请原谅我无法为你感到开心
Forgive me if I'm having trouble being happy for you.
小傻瓜  痛在你身  乐在我心
Don't be silly, I'm loving your pain.
这会是我俩结婚以后的状态吗
Is this how our marriage is going to be?
有时候人们会更愿意和她说话
Sometimes people will be more interested
而不是和我说话吗
in talking to her than to me?
你现在人在厕所吗
Are you sitting in a bathroom?
是的
Yes.
我需要一个能让我摔门冲入的地方
I needed a place to storm off to
这里是唯一可以的地方
and it was all that was available.
好吧
Fine.
但如果有冲马桶的声音  谈话立刻结束
But if I hear a flush, this conversation is over.
那些人的面前有一位世界级的智者
Those people were in the presence of a world-class mind,
而他们却只想聊那些无聊废话
and all they wanted to talk about was their own nonsense.
你能听出其中的讽刺意味吗
Can you see the irony in that statement?
听出来没
How about now?
现在呢
我等你慢慢想
I'll wait.
惊喜
Surprise.
糟了  今天是我们的纪念日吗
Oh, crap, is it our anniversary?
不  等一下
No. Wait.
-不  -不是
- No. - No.
好吧  那我们是在庆祝什么事
All right, so what are we celebrating?
你知道  博纳黛特和霍华德又怀孕了
Well, you know, Bernadette and Howard are pregnant again,
艾米和谢尔顿也要结婚了
and Amy and Sheldon are getting married.
我不想让你感到受冷落
I didn't want you to feel left out.
什么  受冷落吗
Ah. Left out?
博纳黛特肚子里要长一个小宝宝
Well, Bernadette has to grow a baby inside of her,
艾米马上要嫁给另一个小宝宝
and Amy has to marry one.
我的人生非常圆满
My life is great.
所以你不想吃这蛋糕了吗
So do you not want the cake?
你把它端走试试  看你怎么死
Try and take it away, see what happens.
糟了  今天真是我们结婚纪念日
Oh, crap, it is our anniversary.
结婚纪念日快乐
Happy anniversary!
艾米
Amy.
有些事我要告诉你
There's something I need to say to you.
我听着呢
I'm listening.
我一直在想复仇者联盟
I've been thinking about the Avengers.
我相信
I believe that.
但我觉得这没什么好跟我说的
But I don't think that's something you needed to say to me.
我意识到钢铁侠超屌
I realized that Iron Man is great.
但同时  美国队长也很不错
And also, that Captain America is great.
有时钢铁侠还会出现在美国队长的电影里
And sometimes, Iron Man is in a Captain America movie,
他也不会因为这不是钢铁侠电影而生气
and he's not mad it's not an Iron Man movie.
他只是帅气飞来  让观众热血沸腾
You know, he can fly in, give the audience a thrill,
然后再霸气飞走
and then fly away.
我今晚应该这么表现才对
And that should've been me tonight.
我应该当你电影中的讨喜龙套
I should've been the delightful cameo in your movie.
谢谢你  谢尔顿
Thank you, Sheldon.
相反的  我表现得像暴怒的绿巨人一样...
Instead, I was like the Hulk, and I...
够了  请不要再提复仇者联盟了
Okay, please stop talking about the Avengers.
总而言之
Anyway.
我为你骄傲
I'm proud of you.
我以后会尽量学习分享目光焦点
And I'm going to try to do a better job
因为我们是同一个队的
of sharing the spotlight because we're a team.
你懂吗  我们就像是棒球道奇队的球员
You know? Much like t-the Dodgers.
如果他们有超能力  会打击犯罪
If they had superpowers, and fought crime.
而且雷神索尔也在队里
And Thor was in them.
谢尔顿  我知道这很不容易
Sheldon, I know this isn't easy,
但你会有一辈子来慢慢练习
but you'll have a whole lifetime to practice.
也许真的需要这么久  我对此非常不在行
I-It could take that long, I'm really bad at it.
也许...
You know, maybe, um,
我该从现在开始  赶紧回帕萨迪纳
I should start right now, and go back to Pasadena
让你好好独自享受这一切
and let you have this experience to yourself.
你就是想回到那个
You just want to go back
大家都稀罕你的地方吧
'cause that's where everybody makes a fuss over you.
你的同事说得对  你真是冰雪聪明
You know, your colleagues are right, you are brilliant.
3个月后
你们好呀
Hello.
艾米  欢迎回来
Amy, welcome back.
让我看看订婚戒指
Oh, l-let me see the ring.
美死了
Ooh, nice.
喂喂  别乱看呀
H-Hey, her eyes are up there.
那就是亲了谢尔顿的女人吗
I-Is that the woman who kissed Sheldon?
-有可能  -很难说  跟我们说说普林斯顿的事
- Uh... Could be. - Hard to say. Tell us about Princeton.
请稍等我一会儿
Excuse me for a minute.
不  我们之后再聊
Not-- well, we'll catch up later.
这将是自从我的阿姨在家族聚会上
This is going to be the biggest smackdown
和我表姐穿了同样的沙丽之后
since my Aunt Noopur showed up at the family reunion
最大的一次撕逼大战了
wearing the same sari as my cousin Sruti.
诺维茨基博士
Dr. Nowitzki?
福勒博士  你好
Dr. Fowler. Um, hello.
谢谢  我衷心谢谢你全家
Thank you. Thank you so much.